Nikita Osipov

telegram github linkedin nikitaosipov.51@gmail.com

Location: Georgia

Format: full-time, remote or hybrid in Tbilisi

With over 5 years of versatile developer background and 3+ years of commercial experience in the JS/TS/React frontend world, I'm passionate about creating user-friendly web apps and solving unique problems. Versed in architectural and design patterns such as Domain Driven Design, Feature-Sliced Design and Clean Architecture. I also have some skills in backend frameworks (NestJS, Express) and Docker.

Currently seeking a job!

Skills

Frontend

JavaScript TypeScript React Effector Redux Redux Toolkit NextJS React Query GraphQL React Hook Form ChartJS NX Turborepo Astro Webpack Vite Performance Optimization Contract-first

Backend

Strapi NodeJS ExpressJS NestJS PostgreSQL Python C#

UI

Tailwind CSS SCSS ShadCN/Radix Adobe Spectrum Material UI Responsive Design

Testing

Jest Vitest Cypress React Testing Library TDE

Miscellaneous

English B1+ Docker SEO

Work experience

Independent Contractor

Frontend Developer

march 2023 - now

- Was involved in launching and managing several personal web projects.
- Participated as a freelancer.
- Engaged as volunteer or consultant within several developer communities.

Sber

Frontend Developer

april 2021 - april 2023

- Launched 2 new projects and refactored 3 existing ones.
 Developed six gaming web applications as part of special projects, and created two
- educational courses about investments.

 Destining the development of a unified CMS for content websites in the cluster
- Participated in the development of a unified CMS for content websites in the cluster.
 Mentored three developers and led two product teams.

Business IntegrationFrontend Developer

december 2020 - april 2021

Pofactored a corvice dachb

Refactored a service dashboard displaying the internal services status at the bank.

Triumph group of companies Frontend Developer

september 2019 - september 2020

• Developed around 80 tools for the browser-based editor for clothing items, including UI

- and functionality.
 Participated in the development of tools for sewing patterns on a 3D mannequin.
- Contributed to backlog planning.
- Mentored 6 new programmers.
- Web games development, Phaser.js

november 2018 - july 2019

Developer

Wrote about six games in TypeScript and Phaser.js for the portfolio.

- Completed approximately 400 tasks on basic algorithms during training.
 Collaborated with another programmer to develop a commercial game-s
- Collaborated with another programmer to develop a commercial game-special project, a runner based on duck stories.
- runner based on duck stones.

Developer

RD Express

june 2018 - november 2018

• Designed and developed Telegram, WhatsApp, VK, and Viber bots, consisting of 4

- separate services (showcase, product search, delivery processing, inventory checking) for organizing fulfillment for a comics delivery company.

 Integrated with external services Dostavista and MoySklad.

GMsite

GMsite

Web Developer june 2018 - november 2018

- Closed around 100 support tasks for existing clients of the company.
- Created a new design from scratch for two websites, totaling around 20 separate pages.

<u>telegram</u> <u>github</u> <u>linkedin</u> nikitaosipov.51@gmail.com